Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Ben and Jerry's flavors but
lower in calories and higher in protein.
This is chocolatey love affair. Let me
show you how to make it. To make the
chocolate base, we're going in with one
chocolate protein shake. Either a
pre-made one or you can make one with
chocolate protein powder and milk. Then
some extra sweetener, salt, zantham gum,
and some cocoa powder to bring out all
the flavors and give it a nice rich
chocolate flavor. Funny thing about this
flavor is that I didn't even know it
existed. I think it's only in the UK.
It's a collab with Tony's Chocolatoni.
Chocolate. I don't even know what it's
called, but I know it's an amazing
flavor combination. And to recreate that
salted fudge chunk aspect they have. I'm
using the Hornbulls salted fudge flavor.
Coincidentally, Hornbulls just
rebranded. They removed EPG from their
bars. I'm not going to speculate as to
why, but I think we all know. And now
they taste even better. They're richer,
denser, they taste more chocolatey in my
opinion. So, I'm loving the rebrand.